(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)ディオ様！
(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)
別のボディーさえあれば…｡
I have to move my arm...
...before the Ripple reaches my head... Before it...
Before it-!
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)〈1888年12月４日付け
ロンドン･プレス紙より 抜粋｡➡
｢山あいの小さな町
ウインドナイツ･ロットで➡
一夜にして 人口452人のうち
73名が 行方不明となる｡➡
原因は 捜査中｡➡
関係すると思われる
目撃情報は１件｡➡
Master Dio...
４人のよそ者が➡
If only he had a new body...
東の崖下にあった男性の服を
拾い集め 焼き捨てていた｡➡
そのうちの１人は
奇怪な仮面を 館から持ち出し➡
And so it was written in the London Press,
on December 4th, 1888:
ハンマーで 粉々に砕いた
という｣〉
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)これで決着よ！
Earlier this month, 73 of the 452 residents went missing
in the small mountain town of Wind Knight's Lot.
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
"The police are still on the lookout."
"There was only one eyewitness report."
♬ 空 こぼれ落ちたふたつの星が
"Four outsiders were sighted at the bottom
of the eastern cliff as they burned a pile of clothing."
♬ 光と闇の水面
吸い込まれてゆく
"One of the suspects was seen taking a strange mask from the mansion, and later witnessed crushing it to pieces with a hammer."
♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
That settles that!
♬～
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬～
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Speedwagon
Distro:
ExWizzard
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
♬～
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 9: "The Final Ripple!"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)｢ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ家の継承者｡
ジョナサン･ジョースター氏と➡
"The head of the Joestar family, Mr. Jonathan Joestar..."
ペンドルトン家の一人娘
エリナ嬢 結婚！➡
"...and the daughter of the Pendleton family, Miss Erina, have become married!"
"They're expected to honeymoon in America," huh?
ハネムーンは アメリカへ｣か｡
あっ！➡
おっと！
もう こんな時間だ！➡
Oh no! Look at the time!
ジョースターさんたち
出ちまうぜ！
Mr. Joestar's gonna be leaving soon!
≪(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)お～い！
Hey!
Mr. Speedwagon!
(ポコ)スピードワゴンさ～ん！
How can you be so late when you're seeing someone off?
見送りが遅れちゃあ
駄目じゃんか！
My bad, my bad!
悪い 悪い！ で ２人は？
So where are they?
They're already on board.
とっくに乗っちゃったよ｡
え～!?
(ポコ)もうすぐ 出航だもん｡
Eh?!
The boat's leaving soon!
What?!
何!? どこだ どこだ!?
Where?! Where?!
Brother Styx, we hope to hear good news from your mission to Mexico.
(神父)スティクス神父｡➡
メキシコでの宣教活動
期待しとるよ｡
(ｽﾃｨｸｽ)微力を尽くします｡
I shall do my best.
Mr. Joestar! Where are you?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョースターさ～ん！
どこだ～!?
Outta the way!
(男性１)邪魔だ どけ～！
This thing weighs a ton! What the hell could be in here?
まったく 重てえな！
何が入ってんだ!?
How should I know?
(男性２)
知るか｡ ゆうべ 妙な東洋人が来て
頼まれたんだよ｡
Some strange oriental guy payed the fee to load it on board last night.
≪(物音)
ん？
Wrrryyy...
≪WRRRYYY
(男性１)
おい｡ い… 今 何か音が…｡
Hey...
D-Did you hear something?
つべこべ言わずに 積め込め！➡
Cut the complaints and get moving!
あの船に載せなきゃ
金もらえねえぞ！
We don't load this cargo, we don't get paid!
(男性たち)えっほ えっほ｡
That hurt! What was that all about?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)痛え～！ 何だ？ 今の｡
(ポコ)スピードワゴンさん！
Mr. Speedwagon!
Look, there they are!
ほら ２人だよ｡
お～い！
ジョースターさ～ん！
Hey, Mr. Joestar!
It's a damn fine thing!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)《まったく めでたいぜ｡
２人とも 幸せになってくれよ！➡
I wish nothing but happiness for the two of you!
I'll always be there for you guys!
俺は いつまでも 応援するし
困ったときは いつでも➡
If you ever need me, I'll have your back, no matter what!
どんな所でも
駆けつけるつもりだぜ！➡
But knowing me, I'll probably just get in their way.
もっとも
かえって 足手まといかな》
(汽笛)
(ポコ)エヘヘヘ！
Mr. Joestar! Enjoy your trip!
ジョースターさ～ん！➡
お幸せに～！
- The Atlantic Ocean, En Route To America -
(ｴﾘﾅ)あっ｡
渡り鳥が １羽だけ…
みんなと はぐれて…｡
A single bird. It must have gotten separated...
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ)エリナ どうかしたかい？
Erina,
what's the matter?
Why were you crying?
何を 泣いているんだい？
この涙は 幸せの涙です｡
あなたが ここにいることの｡
They're tears of joy...
The joy of having you here.
When we were children, you took out
your handkerchief in front of those bullies,
(ｴﾘﾅ)《子供のころ いじめっ子に
さらに 殴られるのを知っていて➡
even though you knew it would make them go after you instead.
あえて 自分の名の入った
ハンカチを見せた➡
誇り高き ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ･ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰが
この腕の中にいる幸せです》
Being together with the noble Jonathan Joestar is what fills me with such joy.
I feel the same.
《それは 僕も同じさ｡➡
心が 暗く 冷えてしまったとき➡
When my heart was at its coldest,
you were the only warmth it knew...
温かくしてくれたのは
君なのだから》
This is why I'm so happy to have protected the world you live in.
《だからこそ 君の住む
この世界を守れたことが➡
とても うれしい｡➡
I wish father could have met you...
この人を
父さんに 会わせたかった》
Erina...
エリナ さあ 食事に行こう！
Come now, dinner is being served!
Jonathan-!
ジョナサン！
ん？ ぐっ！
か… くぅ…｡
I was just about to tell you to watch your head...
あ… 頭に気を付けて
って言おうとしたところなのに｡
ハハハッ！
ウフフフ｡
(ｴﾘﾅ)《ああ… 今日という日が
永遠に続きますように》
Ah, if only this day could last forever.
For Christ's sake, the engine room?
(ｽﾃｨｸｽ)くそ～ 下は機関室か｡➡
I just had to drop it in the dirtiest place possible.
ダーティーな所に
落としちまったぜ｡
ヒック｡ うっちゃってもいいが…
大事な商売道具だ｡
I don't need it too badly, but it is a tool of the trade.
神よ…｡
My Lord...
You certainly enjoy testing the patience of your humble servant.
(ｽﾃｨｸｽ)
《あんたは この俺を 面倒な所へ
やるのが お好きなようだ》
No thank you... I've never tasted alcohol before.
(ｴﾘﾅ)駄目｡ お酒なんか
飲んだことありませんもの…｡
Just try a bit. One sip won't hurt.
少しさ｡ ほんのちょっぴりだけ｡
I swear, it isn't very strong.
そんなに 強くないからさ｡
試してごらんよ｡
Just try it.
さあ｡
Go on...
あっ！
I-It's him!
お… お前は!?
Jonathan?
ジョナサン？
ま… まさか！ そんなバカな！
It can't be... that's impossible!
ディオが… 生きて…｡
Dio... is still-
(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)フッ｡
あっ！
Erina, go back to the cabin!
エリナ！ 船室へ戻っているんだ｡
And make sure to lock the door behind you!
ドアに 鍵をかけるのを
忘れないで！
♬～
ふん…｡ おや？➡
Huh? What kind of cargo is this?
何だ？ この荷物｡
錠が開いているぞ…｡
What's with this lock?
それに 奇妙だ…｡
How bizarre... I can see the latch on the other side of the lock.
このふたの隙間から見える
留め金が 光って見えるぞ｡
But that would mean this box...
つまり この箱…
中から 鍵がかかっている！
...was locked from the inside?!
はへっ！
Hold it!
待て！ お前は…｡
You're-!
My body... I've found it.
ボディー… 来たか…｡
D-Dio!
ディ… ディオ！
(ｴﾘﾅ)
《さっきの ジョナサンの様子…
普通じゃない！》
Jonathan was acting strange...
Something must be wrong with him.
(女性)キャー！
ジョジョ… 見ろ｡
Jojo, look at what you've done to me, the mighty Dio.
このディオの 情けなき姿を！
あえて… あえて
この姿を お前の前にさらそう｡
Behold... Behold, and I will show you the fruits of my labor.
And why am I showing you this?
なぜ
こんな姿を あえて見せるのか｡
Because, Jojo, despite the hatred I should have,
I now find myself admiring you instead.
それは ジョジョ
あれほど 侮っていたお前を➡
今 尊敬しているからだ｡
勇気を お前の魂を➡
Your courage. Your soul. Your power. I respect it all.
パワーを 尊敬している…｡
それに気付いたからだ｡
This is what I have come to realize.
Dio...
ディオ…｡
Jojo...
ジョジョ… お前がいなかったら➡
Were it not for you,
I would have never come into possession of the stone mask.
このディオに 仮面の力は
手に入らなかっただろう｡
しかし お前がいたから
いまだ 世界は➡
However, you were also the one that kept me from ruling the world.
俺のものになっていない！
神がいるとして
運命を操作しているとしたら！
If there really were a god controlling our fate, I doubt even he could have made two destinies more perfectly intertwined than our own.
俺たちほど よく計算された
関係はあるまい！
ハァ ハァ…｡
You and I are equal parts of a greater whole.
俺たちは この世において
２人で１人！ つまり…｡
And so, I will now seize the body of the only man in the world I truly admire...
俺は この世で ただ１人
尊敬する人間の ﾎﾞﾃﾞｨｰを手に入れ➡
...and I will live on for an eternity!
けんらんたる 永遠を生きる｡
That is the fate of the mighty Dio!
それが このディオの運命なのだ！
苦痛は与えん｡
Your death will be painless; a final act of courtesy towards my rival!
それが
我がライバルへの 最後の礼儀！
ううっ あの目は！
ま… まずい！
Those eyes! This is bad!
You shall live on as my new body, Jojo!
我が肉体となって 生きよ！
ジョジョ～！
ジョナサン！
Jonathan!
Eri... na...
エリ… ナ…｡
ガハッ！
ジョ… ジョナサン！
Jo-Jonathan!
エリ… ナ…｡
Eri... na...
ふぅ… なんということだ｡
What a shame.
Had you not tried to dodge, I would have pierced your brain and granted you an instant death.
なまじ よけなければ
眉間を撃ち抜き➡
苦しみを与えずに
即死させたものを…｡
You're so surprised to see your life descend into
utter hell you've been stricken speechless, is that it?
日常から 一気に魔界へ…｡
どういう事態が起こっているのか
把握できず➡
声も出ない… か｡
Did Jojo not tell you of my legend? My descent into darkness?
ジョジョは 語らなかったのか？
暗黒に生きる この俺の神話を！
Despite this pitiful state, I'm sure you still recognize me... Erina Pendleton.
今は 情けない姿だが
この俺に 見覚えがあるだろう｡
エリナ･ペンドルトン｡
Or should I say, Mrs. Erina Joestar?
いや 今は
ミセス･エリナ･ジョースターかな｡
ディオ！
Dio!
はっ！
≪(男性の叫び声)
(男性)船中が 化け物だらけだ！
This ship is teeming with monsters!
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ１)OHHHH！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ２)MHOOO！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ２)MHOOOO！
あ…｡
(赤ん坊の泣き声)
(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)ウェヘヘヘヘ！
By your command, I feasted on the blood of a single crewman,
and now the entire ship is filled with our brethren!
ご命令どおり
私が １人の血を吸いましたので➡
既に 船内は ほとんど
同胞に変わってまさあ！➡
ヒャヒヒヒッ！
And now we shall all make our way to America, won't we, Master Dio?
そして このまま アメリカまで
行くのですね？ ディオ様｡
《声が出ない｡ いや それより
息ができないんだ｡➡
I-I can't speak...
But more importantly... I can't breathe-!
呼吸が…｡
エリナ… ああ エリナ…》
Erina...
Erina!
ガハッ！
I have to... save you-!
君だけは…｡
《は… 波紋が練れない…》
I can't channel the Ripple-!
KAHH！ ディオ様 見てくだせえ！
Master Dio, look!
This worthless pile of filth can't breathe!
この くそったれ野郎！
呼吸ができませんぜ｡➡
He can't use that Ripple thing either!
つまり 波紋とやらは
使えんわけだ！
Should I begin shredding you to pieces for reducing Master Dio to this state?
ディオ様を こんな姿にした報い！
なぶってやりやしょうかね…｡
それとも あと数分でしょうか｡
Or should I wait the few minutes that it will take for you to bleed out?
窒息するのを 楽しみますかね？
Enough, Wang Chung!
おい ワンチェン！
There shall be no disrespect towards Jojo!
ジョジョへの侮辱は 許さんぞ！
えっ？
He was the only mortal capable of reducing me to this state.
彼は このディオを
こんな姿にまで 追い込んだ人間｡
You will honor his accomplishment by
quickly and painlessly slicing off his head!
尊敬の念を持って
苦しみを与えず➡
速やかに やつの首を切断しろ！
Y-Yes, Master Dio!
は… はい ディオ様｡
And with that, my friend's body shall become my future!
そして この友のボディーは
我がフューチャーとなる！
Johnathan!
ジョナサン！
な… 妙な動きに気を付けろ！
一旦 引け！
Be careful with his strange movements! Stand back!
He's going to take a gamble on a last ditch attack!
こいつは 最後の最後に
何か やるかもしれぬ！
There's nothing to fear!
《な～に 構うものか｡➡
ディオ様は こいつを
高く評価し過ぎでっせ！》
Master Dio overestimates this filthy dog!
てめえ！ 脳みそを
指で すくい取ってくれる！
I'm going to scoop out your brain with my fingers, you imbecile!
この うすのろめ！
《エリナ… だけは！➡
Erina... not her...
I'll release the last of my Ripple energy at once...
体内に残された
かすかな 最後の波紋…｡➡
...no matter how little I have left!
全てを 一気に放出する｡
かすかでいい！》
Th-This is bad! Wang Chung!
なっ ヤバい ワンチェン！
あっ！
《き… 切れた｡
僕の体の中で 何かが切れた｡➡
It's gone... Something inside of me is gone...
決定的な何かが…》
Something vital...
うわっ！
ま… まずい！
This isn't good!
Th-That... That was the last of my life force...
《こ… これが…
これが 僕の ｢生命｣…➡
My life's final Ripple... and it was too weak to destroy that zombie...
生命最後の波紋だ…｡➡
よ… 弱くって あのゾンビを
完全に 破壊できないが…｡➡
これで 十分だ…》
But it should be... just enough...
な… 何!? これは！
W-What?!
Jojo must have done something to Wang Chung's body!
ワンチェンの体に
ジョジョは 何かしたのだ！
That Ripple didn't destroy his body,
but it was enough to manipulate his movements!
波紋は ワンチェンの体を破壊せず
体組織の機能を 狂わしたのか！
And now Wang Chung is clinging to that machinery like he's being possessed.
ワンチェンは 操られたように
機械を がっしり つかんでいる｡
A-And by doing that he's going to stop...
そ… そして ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝがつかんで
止めようとしているのは!?
...the ship's guiding screw shaft!
船の外輪スクリューシャフト！
A zombie is more than strong enough to stop that shaft!
ゾンビの怪力なら➡
シャフトの動きを
止めることは可能！
And with it stopped, the steam inside the ship's pistons will have nowhere to escape, causing the pressure to rise!
シャフトが止まれば ピストン内の
蒸気の逃げ道はなくなり➡
圧力は 高まる一方➡
圧力が
鉄壁の耐久度を 超えたとき…｡
Which means once the pressure reaches a certain point... the ship will explode!
船は 爆発する！
おお ジョナサン｡
こんなことが…｡
Jonathan...
How did this... How could this have happened... Why?!
こんな まさか… なぜ？
Get out of here, Erina...
に… 逃げるんだ エリナ｡
この船を ば… 爆発させる…｡
The ship is... going to explode...
私には 一体 どんな事態が
起こっているのか 分かりません｡
I don't understand why this is happening...
だって… 想像を超えていて
泣けばいいのか 叫べばいいのか➡
I never imagined this happening...
I don't know if I want to cry, scream, or maybe just faint...
それとも 気を失えばいいのか
分からないのですもの…｡
I just don't know.
However, there is one thing I do know.
でも… 言えることは ただ１つ｡
エリナ･ジョースターは…｡
I, Erina Joestar...
...will die at your side!
あなたと共に 死にます｡
I can tell from the warmth of his lips...
(ｴﾘﾅ)
《この唇の ぬくもりの中には…➡
Why is this happening? I can feel death enveloping him...
ああ なんてこと｡
死の実感がある…｡➡
ジョナサン･ジョースターは
死ぬんだわ｡➡
Jonathan Joestar is going to die... but, as long as he's alive...
でも ２人一緒なら
ずっと こうしていたい…》
...I will stay by his side.
Until the ship explodes. Until everything turns to embers... Until everything is gone.
(ｴﾘﾅ)《船が爆発し
何もかも 燃えてしまうまで…｡➡
何もかも 消えてしまうまで…》
(赤ん坊の泣き声)
あ… ああ！
泣いてくれても… いい…｡
Let the tears flow if you must... but please... survive...
でも 君は…
生きなくては… ならない…｡
ああ！ う… 美しすぎます！
H-How is such nobility even possible?
You're willing to die, and only to save the life of someone else's child!
見ず知らずの 女性の赤ちゃんを
救って 避難しろとおっしゃるの？
うう… 私にとって
それは 残酷なる勇気！
Your courage can be so cruel!
All that I wish for is to die by your side!
私の最後の希望は
あなたと共に 死ねることなのに｡
あの母親は
子供をかばって… 死んでいる｡
That mother... sacrificed herself... for her child...
僕の母も… そうして死んだ｡
The same... as my mother did for me...
あの子を連れて… 早く…｡
Take the child... Take it... and hurry!
So, you plan to blow this ship to pieces?!
船ごと
爆破させようという思いつき！
Jojo, even with these last breaths, your obstinance is remarkable!
ジョジョ！ 最後の最後まで
屈服しないやつよ！
But the mighty Dio can be just as obstinate!
しかし
それは このディオも同じこと！
I will survive! No matter what it takes!
俺は生きる
何が何でも 生きる！
And I'll be taking your body along with me!
貴様の肉体と共にな！
Zombies!
ゾンビども！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞたち)UGAAA！
ワンチェンを食ってしまえ！
Devour Wang Chung! Get those pistons moving again!
そして
ピストンを再稼動させろ！
It's going to begin exploding soon...
《爆発が… 始まる…》
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞたち)UGAAA！
ああっ！
ああっ！ ジョナサン！
Jonathan!
ぬう… 爆発が始まったか！
The explosion is starting!
だが このディオ 太陽から
常に 身を守らねばならぬ宿命｡
But I, the mighty Dio, must always protect myself from the sun!
I'm more than prepared to withstand a little explosion!
大爆発程度の事態は
既に 防御策を講じてあるのよ！
ああ！
Erina! Take a good look!
エリナ！ よ～く見てろ！
With Jojo unable to create a Ripple,
I can take control of his body with ease!
ジョジョのやつが
波紋を出せない 今！
俺は安心して
その肉体を乗っ取れる！
そして 俺は
自分のベッドルームである➡
And then, I shall retreat to my bedroom in that box!
あの箱に 逃れるのだ！
あの箱は 爆薬 数十樽の
衝撃にも耐えうる｡
It's capable of withstanding an absolutely massive explosion!
いわば １人用シェルターよ！
Consider it a bomb shelter made for one!
行くぞ！ ジョジョ！
Here I come, Jojo!
And I bid welcome to my new, immortal body!
そして ようこそ！
我が永遠の肉体よ！
なっ！ うわあ…｡
Jonathan!
ジョナサン！
うっ…｡
Dio...
《ディオ…》
《君の言うように
僕らは やはり➡
You could be right...
The two of us may very well be inseparable by fate.
２人で１人
だったのかもしれないな》
I even feel like I have some kind of bizarre friendship with you...
《奇妙な友情すら感じるよ｡➡
And now our fates are truly one in the same...
今 ２人の運命は
完全に １つになった｡➡
そして 船の爆発で消える…》
We will both vanish in the explosion of this ship.
Find... happiness... Erina...
幸せに… エリナ…｡
Let go of me... Jojo!
放せ… ジョジョ～！ 放すんだ｡
Let go of me! Just think about it, Jojo!
考え直せ ジョジョ！
お前にも
永遠をやろうではないか！
I can grant you immortality as well!
I'll heal your wounds. You can spend eternity with Erina!
その傷も治す！
エリナと 永遠を生きられるぞ
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
ジョジョ!?
Jojo?!
H-He...
こ… こいつ…｡
He's dead...
死んでいる…｡
February 7th, 1889
Jonathan Joestar passes away
(ｴﾘﾅ)《ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ･ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰの人生は
忘却のかなたに 消え去りました》
Jonathan Joestar's life vanished in the depths of eternity.
He spent his life in the shadows of history
that the world will never truly know.
(ｴﾘﾅ)
《それは 世の中の人々には➡
決して 知られることのない
影の歴史です》
Society will never know the story of the proud life that he lived.
(ｴﾘﾅ)《彼の生きた
誇り高き人生の物語は➡
世間に聞こえることは
決して ありませんが…》
(ｴﾘﾅ)《彼の子孫には
聞こえるでしょう》
However, his descendants will.
(ｴﾘﾅ)《あのとき…
私の体内に宿りつつあった➡
The new life growing inside me will know the truth.
新しい生命には
きっと 聞こえるでしょう》
Erina Joestar was rescued off the coast of the Canary Islands two days later.
〈２日後
エリナ･ジョースターは➡
カナリア諸島沖で 救助された｡➡
そして 石仮面の伝説は
ひとまず 幕を下ろす｡➡
And for now, the curtain falls on the legend of the stone mask...
However! This was only the beginning of a new age of adventure!
しかし！ それはまた➡
新たな冒険の時代の
始まりでもあった〉
Part 1: Phantom Blood
The End
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
♬ I spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
The music dance and sing
♬ The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
♬ Spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
Next Episode
It was 1938...
It's been a while, Speedwagon.
How'd you know about my brass knuckles, you little punk?!
Deal with him!
Joseph Joestar. But just call me Jojo.
Episode 10:
"New York's Jojo"
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)あれは 1938年の秋｡
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)お久しぶりです
スピードワゴンさん｡
(男性)何で メリケンのこと
分かったんだ!? この野郎！
(ｴﾘﾅ)きちっと やっつけなさい！
ジョセフ･ジョースター｡
ジョジョって呼んでくれ｡